<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Data Science Journey on Jade Affolabi</title>
    <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Data Science Journey on Jade Affolabi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project II : Ongoing</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX XXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXXX</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project I</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>In order to learn more about python I took a time in my summer to polish up the core concepts of python such as classes, special methods, exceptions, virtual environment, unit tests etc. To apply what I had learned I redo an academic project that I had done in C the same year since it was quite challenging at that time. It is a program that is able to compress and decompress a file using the Huffman data compression algorithm.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>Although I study computer science, my interest in mathematics drives my desire to pursue a career in Data Science. I am also committed to promoting the responsible use of AI, focusing on developing technologies but also considering ethical implications. A fun fact about me: I love experimenting with new pastry recipes as a way to challenge myself.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Feel free to reach out to me via any of the social media outlets below.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
