<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jade Affolabi</title>
    <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jade Affolabi</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project III : Facial Recognition (Ongoing)</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With a team of three, me and my friends are implementing facial recognition on a Pepper robot.&#xA;The first goal is to allow the robot to distinguish between male and female.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are using ROS (Robot Operating System) and python as programming language.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project II : Personal mobile application (Ongoing)</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am developing my own mobile app. In order to better manage my hobby (Try out new recipes in pastry)&#xA;I need a way to separate the recipes (Youtube videos) that I have tried from those I have not tried yet.&#xA;Morever, for each tried recipes I need to add the pictures of the result and write how it was carried out because I usually do not utterly follow the recipe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Project I : Huffman Compressor</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In order to learn more about python I took a time in my summer to polish up the core concepts&#xA;of python such as classes, special methods, exceptions, virtual environment, unit tests etc.&#xA;To apply what I had learned I redo an academic project that I had done in C the same year since it was&#xA;quite challenging at that time. It is a program that is able to compress and decompress a file using&#xA;the Huffman data compression algorithm.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Projects : Other Projects</title>
      <link>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This section presents briefly some  academic projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;little-robot&#34;&gt;Little robot.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://jadeaffolabi.github.io/Jade_Portfolio/Jade_Portfolio/images/photo_robot_elec.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Little Robot&#34; style=&#34;display : block; margin-right : auto; margin-left : auto;&#34;/&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to apply what we had learned during the practical sessions in Electronics for embedded systems we were challenged to program and control a two-wheeled robot. For this project to be considered a success, two conditions had to be met. Firstly, the robot had to be able to follow a path on its own, making sure to detect obstacles, and secondly, it had to be controllable by remote control. In groups of three, we worked for two months to ensure that our robot passed both the manual and autonomous demonstrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
